Guide to the Stuart Sherman Papers, 1945-2001 (Bulk 1961-2001) MSS.192
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Artwork
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, 1990-1999 (Box 5A, Folder 104)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes - w/ drafts by Tom Zummer, 1991-1992 (Box 5A, Folder 105)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 5A, Folder 106)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, 1991-1993 (Box 5A, Folder 107)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, undated (Box 5A, Folder 108)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, undated (Box 5A, Folder 109)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, undated (Box 5A, Folder 110)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, undated (Box 5A, Folder 111)
  - Drawings, Sketches for Sculpture, Notes, undated (Box 5A, Folder 112)
  - Draft Drawings - Sculpture [photocopies w/ notes], 1985 (Box 5A, Folder 113)
  - Original Drafts - Sculpture, 1985-1989 (Box 5A, Folder 114)
  - Original Drafts - Sculpture [5 drawings on foamboard], 1985 (Box 5A, Folder 115)
  - Original Drafts - Sculpture [4 drawings on foamboard], undated (Box 5A, Folder 116)
  - Original Drafts - Sculpture [5 drawings on foamboard], undated (Box 5A, Folder 117)
  - Original Drafts - Sculpture, undated (Box 5A, Folder 118)
  - Original Drafts - Sculpture, undated (Box 5A, Folder 119)
  - Original Drafts ***Mold damaged artwork (Box 5B, Folder 120)
  - Original Drafts ***Mold damaged artwork (Box 5B, Folder 121)
  - Transparencies - Drafts for Sculpture, undated (Box 5A, Folder 122)
  - Collage - List of artworks, 1995-1996 (Box 5A, Folder 123)
  - Collage works, 1995-1996 (Box 5A, Folder 124)
  - Collage works, 1995-1997 (Box 5A, Folder 125)
  - Collage works, 1995-1997 (Box 5A, Folder 126)
  - Collage works - "Book of Colors", 1/25/96, 1995-1996 (Box 5A, Folder 127)
  - Collage works - "Asses to Asses" [orig. housed in binder], 1996 (Box 5A, Folder 128)
  - Collage works - [orig. housed in binder], 1996-1997 (Box 5A, Folder 129)
  - Collage works - w/ exhibition sign, May 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 5A, Folder 130)
  - Collage works, 1999 (Box 5A, Folder 131)
  - Collage works, drawings, notes, poetry - 2/01-7/01, 2001 (Box 5A, Folder 132)
  - Collage works and drawing, undated (Box 5A, Folder 133)
  - Paper sculpture/collage, undated (Box 5A, Folder 134)
- Series VII: Photographs
  This series includes all negatives, transparencies, contact sheets, and photographic prints from the collection. Some prints and contact sheets include photographer name, performance title, date and other identifying information.
  - Photographs and Negatives - "Stations of the Cross, or the Passion of Stuart", [2001] (Box 6, Folder 12 sleeves)
  - Photographs - "Stations of the Cross, or the Passion of Stuart"; photographer: Herman Sorgeloos, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 3 sleeves)
  - Photographs - "Perfilmance", Anthology Film Archives, 11/5/94; photographer: Larry Miller, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2 sleeves)
  - Photographs and Negatives - [shoes] with note from photographer: Tim Balderstone, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11 sleeves)
  - Contact Sheets - "Room Enough?", 12/30/77; photographer: Nathaniel Tileston, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2 sleeves)
  - Photographs and Negatives - Misc performance, Sculpture, Promotional, etc.; photographers incl. Babette Mangolte, Netty A Mamahit, Christian Blei, et al, undated (Box 6, Folder 39 sleeves)
  - Photographs and Negatives - Misc. personal, family, etc., undated (Box 6, Folder 8 sleeves)
  - Photographs w/ cardboard frame - Parents, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2 sleeves)
  - Photograph w/ cardboard frame - unidentified event, undated (Box 6, Folder 2 sleeves)
- Series VIII: Slides
  This series contains includes two binders of slides documenting Sherman's artistic output. Some slides include detailed identifying information.
  The original order of slides has been preserved, though no obvious rule of arrangement appears to have existed.
  - Slides - Misc. Performance, Exhibit, etc., undated (Box 7, Folder 24 sleeves)
  - Slides - Misc. Performance, Exhibit, etc., undated (Box 8, Folder 21 sleeves)
- Series IX: Video, 63 DVDs
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains contains all videotaped material by or pertaining to Stuart Sherman.
  The materials are arranged into three subseries. Paper material which was found within original video containers may be found in Subseries C. The subseries are labeled as follows:
  Subseries A: Video - Access Copies
  Subseries B: Video - Originals
  Subseries C: Video - Paper Material
  Conditions Governing Access
  Of the media portion, researcher access is limited to Subseries A: Video Recordings – Access Copies. Repository permission is required for access. Please contact Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2596.
  - Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Selections from "The First Spectacle" (perf. on the set of R. Foreman's "Pandering to the Masses"), 4/75, 1975; ID: 192.0220 (Box Shared Fales 145, Dvd 192.0220)
      General note
      Format: DVD
      TRT: 00:26:46
      Source ID: 192.0155
      Original Format: U-matic
    - Selections from Spectacles, 1975-1976, ID: 192.0388 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0388)
      TRT: [00:15:00]
      Source ID: 192.0147
    - "The Second Spectacle" (w/ Stefan Brecht, Richard Foreman, Kate Manheim), [197-]; ID: 192.0217 (Box Shared Fales 145, Dvd 192.0217)
      TRT: 00:45:00
      Source ID: 192.0154
    - Segment from "Sunday" cable tv program, 06/76; pre-production perf.; discussion w/ Jerald Ordover, 1976; ID: 192.0253 (Box Shared Fales 145, Dvd 192.0253)
      TRT: 00:23:37
      Source ID: 192.0034
    - "The Seventh Spectacle", [1976]; ID: 192.0406 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0406)
      TRT: [00:00:00]
      Source ID: 192.0158
    - Selections from Films ("Scotty and Stuart", "Skating", "Flying") and Performances ("11th and 10th Spectacles", "Hamlet", "Oedipus", "Faust", "Chekhov", "Strindberg", "Brecht"), [1977-1986]; ID: 192.0340 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0340)
      TRT: 00:35:00
      Source ID: 192.0141
    - Compilation Tape - selections from Films ("Scotty and Stuart", "Skating", "Flying") and Performances ("11th Spectacle", "10th Spectacle", "Hamlet", "Oedipus", "Faust", "Chekhov"), [1977-1986]; ID: 192.0373 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0373)
      TRT: [00:24:00]
      Source ID: 192.0138
    - Excerpts from "The Classical Trilogy (Hamlet, Oedipus, Faust)" and "The Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)", [1977-1986]; ID: 192.0397 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0397)
      Source ID: 192.0152
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979]; ID: 192.0277 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0277)
      TRT: 00:20:25
      Source ID: 192.0060
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979]; ID: 192.0283 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0283)
      TRT: 00:20:00
      Source ID: 192.0062
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979]; ID: 192.0295 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0295)
      TRT: 00:22:11
      Source ID: 192.0067
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979]; ID: 192.0400 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0400)
      TRT: [00:20:00]
      Source ID: 192.0156
    - 4 videos - "Berlin…" (1986), "Gray Matter" (1987), "Video Walk" (1987), "Five Flowers" (1979), 1979, 1986, 1987; ID: 192.0361 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0361)
      TRT: [00:09:00]
      Source ID: 192.0076
    - "The Thirteenth Spectacle (Language)", 10/17/80, 1980; ID: 192.0244 (Box Shared Fales 145, Dvd 192.0244)
      TRT: 00:38:00
      Source ID: 192.0162
      Original Format: Betamax
    - Tape 1, Language [?], 11/9/80; original unedited material, ID: 192.0334 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0334)
      Source ID: 192.0133A
    - Tape 2, 11/9/80, ID: 192.0385 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0384)
      Source ID: 192.0146
    - "The Tenth Spectacle" - Toulouse Lyon (take 2), St. Petersburg (3), NY (2), Woonsocket (1), Amsterdam (1), Mexico City (1), Woonsochet (2), 1980; ID: 192.0370 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0370)
      Source ID: 192.0137
    - "The Tenth Spectacle", [1980]; ID: 192.0403 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0403)
      Source ID: 192.0157
    - "The Twelfth Spectacle (Language)", 1981; ID: 192.0409 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0409)
      Source ID: 192.0160
    - "The Twelfth Spectacle (Language)", [1981]; ID: 192.0364 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0364)
      TRT: [00:30:00]
      Source ID: 192.0126
    - "Faust - A Portrait by Stuart Sherman", Theater Am Turm, Frankfurt, [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0250 (Box Shared Fales 145, Dvd 192.0250)
      TRT: 00:22:08
      Source ID: 192.0033
    - "Faust" (camera: Lisa), [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0301 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0301)
      TRT: 00:03:44
      Source ID: 192.0031
    - "Faust" (New Approach; camera 2, tape 2), [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0259 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0259)
      TRT: 00:22:22
      Source ID: 192.0053
    - "Faust" #2, MCAD (close-up table, close-up film), [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0298 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0298)
      TRT: 00:08:38
      Source ID: 192.0068
    - "Oedipus", [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0367 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0367)
      Source ID: 192.0129
    - "Oedipus" #1, MCAD (camera 3), [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0292 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0292)
      TRT: 00:20:36
      Source ID: 192.0065
    - "Hamlet, a portrait", [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0391 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0391)
      TRT: [00:25:00]
      Source ID: 192.0149
    - "Hamlet" (tape 2), [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0265 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0265)
      TRT: 00:22:25
      Source ID: 192.0056
    - "Hamlet" (unedited), Tape 5[?] pre-shoot for June 12, [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0289 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0289)
      TRT: 00:22:20
      Source ID: 192.0064
    - "Five Flowers", [1982]; ID: 192.0322 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0322)
      TRT: 00:02:00
    - Performance "Mat. Fac." [?], 10/30/83, 1983; ID: 192.0394 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0394)
      Source ID: 192.0151
    - MIT Hallway [1984/5], 1984-1985; ID: 192.0412 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0412)
      General Note
      TRT: 00:24:00
    - "21 Films", 1984; ID: 192.0349 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0349)
      TRT: 00:50:00
      Source ID: 192.0159
    - "Faust" #1, MCAD (close-up table w/ globes; side shot w/ interruptions; wide shot #2), [1984]; ID: 192.0247 (Box Shared Fales 145, Dvd 192.0247)
      TRT: 00:22:03
      Source ID: 192.0032
    - MIT, [1984/5]; ID: 192.0337 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0337)
      TRT: 00:07:00
      Source ID: 192.0140
    - "Chekhov", MIT (video by Glorianna Davenport/Steve Keuttel), [1984/5]; ID: 192.0358 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0358)
      Source ID: 192.0073
    - "Inside/Outside (Inside an Outsider's View of MIT)", MIT, 3/85, 1985; ID: 192.0256 (Box Shared Fales 145, Dvd 192.0256)
      TRT: 00:22:41
      Source ID: 192.0051
    - "Trilogy" - Brecht, The Kitchen, 6/23/86, 1986; ID: 192.0310 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0310A, Dvd 192.0310B)
      TRT: 00:19:55
      Source ID: 192.0071
    - "Trilogy - Chekhov, Strindberg", The Kitchen (High Speed Dub), [1986]; ID: 192.0307 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0307)
      TRT: 00:21:00
      Source ID: 192.0070
    - "Berlin (West)/ Andere Richtungen", [1986]; ID: 192.0355 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0355)
      TRT: 00:10:00
      Source ID: 192.0125
    - "An Evening of Performance and Film", 6/9/88 (Tape 1 of 2), 1988; ID: 192.0325 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0325)
      Source ID: 192.0130
    - "An Evening of Performance and Film", 6/9/88 (Tape 2 of 2), 1988; ID: 192.0328 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0328)
      Source ID: 192.0131
    - Tape #1 - "SSB, Nancy Tobin, Stalemate, [illegible subtitles], sneezing", [1988]; ID: 192.0271 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0271)
      TRT: 00:20:08
      Source ID: 192.0058
    - "The Fourteenth Spectacle", 8/26/89, 1989; ID: 192.0223 (Box Shared Fales 145, Dvd 192.0223)
      TRT: 00:52:48
      Source ID: 192.0161
      Original Format: VHS
    - "Black-Eyed Susan (Portrait of An Actress)", 1989; ID: 192.0382 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0382)
      TRT: [00:11:00]
      Source ID: 192.0144
    - "Tea" (A intro), [1989]; ID: 192.0376 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0376)
      Source ID: 192.0142
    - "Tea" (B), [1989]; ID: 192.0316 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0316)
      TRT: 01:04:13
      Source ID: 192.0075
    - "Tea" (intro of B+C [?]), [1989]; ID: 192.0319 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0319)
      TRT: 00:51:00
      Source ID: 192.0127
    - "Tea" (C), [1989]; ID: 192.0343 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0343)
      Source ID: 192.0145
    - "The Fifteenth Spectacle: Epoche," 6/23/90, 1990; ID: 192.0418 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0418)
    - Video Mix, Whitney Museum, 11/25/90, 1990; ID: 192.0379 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0379)
      TRT: [00:13:06]
      Source ID: 192.0143
    - "A Glass of Fish", [1993]; ID: 192.0304 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0304)
      TRT: 00:06:45
      Source ID: 192.0069
    - "Liberation (A Portrait of Berenice Reynaud)", [1993]; ID: 192.0331 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0331)
      TRT: 00:08:30
      Source ID: 192.0132
    - "Perfilmance" at Anthology, 11/5/94, 1994; ID: 192.0313 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0313)
      TRT: 01:02:19
      Source ID: 192.0074
    - ["Spectacle" 6/17/97], 1997; ID: 192.0415 (Box Shared Fales 143, Dvd 192.0415)
      TRT: 01:04:00
    - Stuart Sherman segment from KRMA-TV production of "Season Ticket" [interview], undated; ID: 192.0280 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0280)
      Source ID: 192.0061
    - Tape #1 - pre-shoot [unidentified project], undated; ID: 192.0262 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0262)
      TRT: 00:19:09
      Source ID: 192.0055
    - Tape #2 - pre-shoot, June 12, undated; ID: 192.0274 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0274)
      Source ID: 192.0059
    - Tape #2 - original material, [illegible subtitles] "music/ bulls/ mouse", undated; ID: 192.0286 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0286)
      TRT: 00:19:04
      Source ID: 192.0063
    - Tape #3 - "Eyes", undated; ID: 192.0352 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0352)
      TRT: 00:16:05
      Source ID: 192.0052
    - "Forest Fire", undated; ID: 192.0268 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0268)
      TRT: 00:23:08
      Source ID: 192.0057
    - Performance selections, undated; ID: 192.0346 (Box 22, Dvd 192.0346)
      Source ID: 192.0150
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals
    - Performance 8/10/75, 1975; ID: 192.0038 (Box 13, Media ID: 192.0038)
      Format: 1/2" video tape
      TRT: [unknown]
    - Selections from "The First Spectacle" (perf. on the set of R. Foreman's "Pandering to the Masses"), 4/75, 1975; ID: 192.0155 (Box 18, Media ID: 192.0155)
      Format: U-matic
    - "The First Spectacle", 4/15/75 (Cathy Scott), 1975; ID: 192.0193 (Box 20, Media ID: 192.0193)
      Format: 1/2" reel
    - Stuart Sherman's Spectacles - Selections 1975-1976, ID: 192.0091 (Box 15, Media ID: 192.0091)
    - Selections from Spectacles, 1975-1976, ID: 192.0147 (Box 17, Media ID: 192.0147)
    - "The Second Spectacle" (part 1), [197-]; ID: 192.0041 (Box 13, Media ID: 192.0041)
    - "The Second Spectacle" (w/ Stefan Brecht, Richard Foreman, Kate Manheim), [197-]; ID: 192.0154 (Box 18, Media ID: 192.0154)
    - ["The Fourth Spectacle" ?], [197-]; ID: 192.0194 (Box 20, Media ID: 192.0194)
    - Segment from "Sunday" cable tv program, 06/76; pre-production perf.; discussion w/ Jerald Ordover, 1976; ID: 192.0034 (Box 13, Media ID: 192.0034)
    - "The Seventh Spectacle" (with 30 Performers), 1976; ID: 192.0035 (Box 13, Media ID: 192.0035)
    - "The Seventh Spectacle" (with 30 Performers), 1976; ID: 192.0036 (Box 13, Media ID: 192.0036)
    - "The Seventh Spectacle" (with 30 Performers), [1976]; ID: 192.0158 (Box 18, Media ID: 192.0158)
    - Compilation Tape - selections from Films ("Scotty and Stuart", "Skating", "Flying") and Performances ("11th and 10th Spectacles", "Hamlet", "Oedipus", "Faust", "Chekhov"), [1977-1986]; ID: 192.0138 (Box 16, Media ID: 192.0138)
    - Selections from Films ("Scotty and Stuart", "Skating", "Flying") and Performances ("11th and 10th Spectacles", "Hamlet", "Oedipus", "Faust", "Chekhov", "Strindberg", "Brecht"), [1977-1986]; ID: 192.0141 (Box 17, Media ID: 192.0141)
    - 4 videos - "Berlin…" (1986), "Gray Matter" (1987), "Video Walk" (1987), "Five Flowers" (1979), 1979, 1986, 1987; ID: 192.0076 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0076)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)", [1979]; ID: 192.0139 (Box 17, Media ID: 192.0139)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)"; and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" from "The Eighth Spectacle", [1979]; ID: 192.0148 (Box 17, Media ID: 192.0148)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979]; ID: 192.0060 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0060)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979]; ID: 192.0062 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0062)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979]; ID: 192.0067 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0067)
    - Selections from "The Eleventh Spectacle (The Erotic)" and "Portrait of Stuart Sherman" (from "The Eighth Spectacle"), [1979]; ID: 192.0156 (Box 18, Media ID: 192.0156)
    - Tape 1, "Language" [?], 11/9/80; original unedited material, 192.0133A (Box 16, Media 192.0133A)
    - "The Tenth Spectacle" - Coconut Grove FL (take 3), Harper Kansas (4), Cairo (3), Copenhagan (2), London (3), Paris (3), Geneva (2), Amsterdam, Corfn[?] (2), Tokyo Milan (3), San Francisco (2), Istanbul (2), 1980; ID: 192.0136 (Box 16, Media ID: 192.0136)
    - "The Tenth Spectacle" - Toulouse Lyon (take 2), St. Petersburg (3), NY (2), Woonsocket (1), Amsterdam (1), Mexico City (1), Woonsochet (2), 1980; ID: 192.0137 (Box 16, Media ID: 192.0137)
    - "The Tenth Spectacle", [1980]; ID: 192.0157 (Box 18, Media ID: 192.0157)
    - Tape 2, 11/9/80, ID: 192.0146 (Box 17, Media ID: 192.0146)
    - "The Thirteenth Spectacle (Language)", 10/17/80, 1980; ID: 192.0162 (Box 18, Media ID: 192.0162)
      Format: Betamax
      TRT: 0038:00
    - "3=1 (A Careful Misreading)" based on poems by Stefan Brecht, Edwin Denby, Peter Frank; Performers: Mickey Greenall and Fiona Templeton; Mickery Theater, Amsterdam, 1980; ID: 192.0167 (Box 19, Media ID: 192.0167)
    - "The Twelfth Spectacle (Language)", 1981; ID: 192.0160 (Box 18, Media ID: 192.0160)
    - "The Twelfth Spectacle (Language)", [1981]; ID: 192.0126 (Box 16, Media ID: 192.0126)
    - "Faust (A Portrait)", Theater Am Turm, Frankfurt, [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0163 (Box 19, Media ID: 192.0163)
    - "Faust (A Portrait by Stuart Sherman)", Theater Am Turm, Frankfurt, [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0033 (Box 13, Media ID: 192.0033)
    - "Faust" (camera: Lisa), [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0031 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0031)
    - "Faust" (New Approach; camera 2, tape 2), [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0053 (Box 13, Media ID: 192.0053)
    - "Oedipus", [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0128 (Box 16, Media ID: 192.0128)
    - "Hamlet, a portrait", [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0149 (Box 17, Media ID: 192.0149)
    - "Hamlet", [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0087 (Box 15, Media ID: 192.0087)
      Format: VHS
    - "Hamlet", [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0189 (Box 20, Media ID: 192.0189)
      Format: Hi8
    - "Hamlet" (tape 2), [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0056 (Box 13, Media ID: 192.0056)
    - "Hamlet" (unedited), Tape 5[?] pre-shoot for June 12, [1981-1984]; ID: 192.0064 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0064)
    - Excerpts from "The Classical Trilogy (Hamlet, Oedipus, Faust)" and "The Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)", [1981-1986]; ID: 192.0152 (Box 17, Media ID: 192.0152)
    - Excerpts from "The Classical Trilogy (Hamlet, Oedipus, Faust)" and "The Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)", [1981-1986]; ID: 192.0153 (Box 17, Media ID: 192.0153)
    - Excerpts from "The Classical Trilogy (Hamlet, Oedipus, Faust)" and "The Second Trilogy (Chekhov, Strindberg, Brecht)", [1981-1986]; ID: 192.0135 (Box 16, Media ID: 192.0135)
    - "Five Flowers", [1982]; ID: 192.0129 (Box 16, Media ID: 192.0129)
    - Performance "Mat. Fac." [?], 10/30/83, 1983; ID: 192.0151 (Box 17, Media ID: 192.0151)
    - "Theater for New City" [?] (shot by Taka Iimura), 1983; ID: 192.0170 (Box 19, Media ID: 192.0170)
    - "Hamlet", MCAD Performance, 4/84, 1984; ID: 192.0072 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0072)
    - "Hamlet", MCAD Performance, 4/84, 1984; ID: 192.0164 (Box 19, Media ID: 192.0164)
      TRT: [00:17:00]
    - "Oedipus", MCAD Performance, 4/84, 1984; ID: 192.0166 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0166)
      TRT: [00:18:30]
    - "Oedipus" #1, MCAD (camera 3), [1984]; ID: 192.0065 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0065)
    - "Oedipus" #3, MCAD Performance (camera 3), [1984]; ID: 192.0066 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0066)
    - "Faust" #1, MCAD (close-up table w/ globes; side shot w/ interruptions; wide shot #2), [1984]; ID: 192.0032 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0032)
    - "Faust" #2, MCAD (close-up table, close-up film), [1984]; ID: 192.0068 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0068)
    - "21 Films", 1984; ID: 192.0159 (Box 18, Media ID: 192.0159)
    - "21 Films", [1984]; ID: 192.0169 (Box 19, Media ID: 192.0169)
    - MIT Hallway, [1984/5]; ID: 192.0018 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0018)
    - MIT, [1984/5]; ID: 192.0140 (Box 17, Media ID: 192.0140)
    - "Inide/Outside (Inside an Outsider's View of MIT)", MIT, 3/85, 1985; ID: 192.0051 (Box 13, Media ID: 192.0051)
    - "Chekhov", MIT, 1985; ID: 192.0086 (Box 15, Media ID: 192.0086)
    - "Chekhov", MIT (video by Glorianna Davenport/Steve Keuttel), [1985]; ID: 192.0073 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0073)
    - "Chekhov", [1985/6]; ID: 192.0089 (Box 15, Media ID: 192.0089)
    - "Chekhov", wide angle 2, [1985/6]; ID: 192.0002 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0002)
      Format: Betacam
    - "Chekhov", Reel #3, [1985/6]; ID: 192.0003 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0003)
    - "Chekhov", Tape #4, [1985/6]; ID: 192.0004 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0004)
    - "Chekhov", #5, [1985/6]; ID: 192.0005 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0005)
    - "Chekhov", #6, [1985/6]; ID: 192.0006 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0006)
    - Interview for "What's On" Cable TV, 1/4/85, 1985; ID: 192.0165 (Box 19, Media ID: 192.0165)
    - "TAAL…" plus "Fire!, Fire!"…, [1986, 1990?]; ID: 192.0082 (Box 15, Media ID: 192.0082)
    - "The Curse of Sentimentality", Central Park Bandshell 8/10/1986, ID: 192.0007 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0007)
      Format: Beta
    - "Curse of…", Summerstage, [1986]; ID: 192.0117 (Box 15, Media ID: 192.0117)
    - "Berlin (West)/ Andere Richtungen", 1986; ID: 192.0027 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0027)
      TRT: [00:06:00]
    - "Berlin (West)/ Andere Richtungen", [1986]; ID: 192.0125 (Box 16, Media ID: 192.0125)
    - "Gates of Dawn" 8/15/86, 1986; ID: 192.0029 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0029)
    - "Gates of Dawn", [1986]; ID: 192.0030 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0030)
    - "Trilogy - Chekhov, Strindberg", The Kitchen, 6/23/86, 1986; ID: 192.0168 (Box 19, Media ID: 192.0168)
    - "Trilogy - Chekhov, Strindberg", The Kitchen (High Speed Dub), [1986]; ID: 192.0070 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0070)
    - "Trilogy - Brecht", The Kitchen, 6/23/86, 1986; ID: 192.0071 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0071)
    - "Brecht", [1986]; ID: 192.0015 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0015)
    - "Brecht and other performances", [1986]; ID: 192.0083 (Box 15, Media ID: 192.0083)
    - "Cabaret"/ "One-Night Stands", La MaMa, 6/16/1987, w/ George Ashley, Perrry Greaves, John Hagan, Anne Iobst, Mark Boone Jr., Georg Osterman, Scotty Snyder, ID: 192.0010 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0010)
    - "One-Night Stands", La MaMa, 6/16/87, 1987; ID: 192.0095 (Box 15, Media ID: 192.0095)
    - "Cabaret", [1987]; ID: 192.0078 (Box 14, Media ID: 192.0078)
    - HOME, 2/22/87, 1987; ID: 192.0017 (Box 12, Media ID: 192.0017)